<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_index on Café Forgot</title>
    <link>http://cafeforgot.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _index on Café Forgot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 21:42:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cafeforgot.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>mila-sullivan</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mila-sullivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 17:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mila-sullivan/</guid>
      <description>Mila Sullivan is a ready-to-wear line based in Brooklyn, New York, which was founded by three Pratt Institute graduates. Mila Sullivan creates one-of-a-kind pieces, often deconstructing and layering vintage home-goods fabrics to create eclectic and nostalgic garments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>paid-actor</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/paid-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 20:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/paid-actor/</guid>
      <description>Paid Actor is the wearable extension of Dessislava Terzieva&amp;rsquo;s fine art practice which is rooted in collage and found object sculpture. Terzeiva explores fashion as a form of communication, the body as a canvas, and the wearer as the messenger. Each piece has it&amp;rsquo;s own unique narrative, whether it is in relation to the imagery/artwork featured on it, or the story behind the material(s) being used. Holistically, the very existence of these one-of-a-kind garments is a statement against fast fashion, trend worship and a look-alike culture fostered by social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zelda-passini</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zelda-passini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zelda-passini/</guid>
      <description>Zelda Passini is a jewelry designer based in Paris. Passini’s work is inspired by postmodern aesthetics, art-deco design and industrial objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tropical-rob</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tropical-rob/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tropical-rob/</guid>
      <description>Tropical Rob serves the hottest fashions du jour. Founded by Robert Hurlbut in 2015, the Los Angeles based line features digital prints of his hand-painted textile designs. TR is a fantasy interpretation of his youth in California, London and at RISD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teva-livne</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/teva-livne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/teva-livne/</guid>
      <description>Teva Livne is a sculptor and artist living in New York. She works with clay, paint and glitter to create an unraveling dream world of shapes, mystery animals, friendship, fantasy and cat charms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>susannah-cutler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susannah-cutler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susannah-cutler/</guid>
      <description>Susannah Cutler is a folk musician and Brooklyn-based textile designer. Her thesis project caught the attention of Café Forgot in the summer of 2018. Her fabrics feature her watercolor drawings of flowers and kittens, which she fashions into breezy sleeveless dresses and crop tops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sophie-andes-gascon</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sophie-andes-gascon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sophie-andes-gascon/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn, New York-based designer Sophie Andes-Gascon produces hand-constructed garments, each with its own story. Andes-Gascon recycles worn fabrics such as dish rags or worker’s uniforms and transforms them into beautiful beaded creations with meticulous attention to detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sara-brooks</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sara-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sara-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn based Sara Brooks makes eclectic clothes that manage to combine a sporty look plus western embellishment and structure with notes of dated sci-fi. She artfully uses seams and fasteners to give shape to her hand-dyed creative creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>poche</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/poche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/poche/</guid>
      <description>Based in Los Angeles, Poche is an atelier that investigates the nuances and constructions of everyday wear and living. They explore the essence of relationships with dress, furnishings and homeware within the context of everyday life. Each piece is hand sewn or outsourced in small batches in Los Angeles as a means of demassification. Poche often uses dead-stock and recycled fabric to create distinctive season-less few-offs. Poche is for everyday use and everyday wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>piera-bochner</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/piera-bochner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/piera-bochner/</guid>
      <description>Piera Bochner is an artist and designer based in Brooklyn, New York, and a long-time friend of Vita and Lucy. Bochner’s candle project comes from a love of wax as a material and a desire to investigate how wicks, wax, and flames can travel down unconventional paths. As they burn, the colorful wax candles cast from romanesco broccoli and bitter melons, become ever-changing sculptural forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pearle-knits</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/pearle-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/pearle-knits/</guid>
      <description>Pearle Knits, is a New York-based label by designer Michaela Pearle from Vancouver, Canada. Her knitwear explores the traditional notions behind women and crafts, and revels in the nostalgia of handmade clothing. Each piece is meticulously handcrafted on a knitting machine in New York and features super-soft, stretchy cotton yarn sourced from mills in Canada and the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onea</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/onea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/onea/</guid>
      <description>The work of New York based artist, Onea Engel-Bradley, asks us to think critically about the ways in which ‘strong’ women are characterized in fashion. Rejecting the ‘power suit,’ her line ranges from sheer romantic elastane dresses to tailored, menswear-inspired linen trousers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nicole-van-vuuren</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/nicole-van-vuuren/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/nicole-van-vuuren/</guid>
      <description>Nicole Van Vuuren is an Auckland, New Zealand based designer exploring fashion through mundane interactions between the body, cloth and garments. After graduating from the fashion program at RMIT University in Melbourne, Australia, she moved to New York, to work in the Eckhaus Latta studio where she and began her current ‘scrap t shirt’ project. Using small pieces of fabric and off-cuts she hand cuts and stitches her enigmatic paneled shirts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>molly-rose-lieberman</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/molly-rose-lieberman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/molly-rose-lieberman/</guid>
      <description>Molly Rose Lieberman is a painter living in Brooklyn, New York. Using found materials, Molly makes wearable objects available at Café Forgot. She also makes small paintings and drawings which have been featured at the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>merritt-deth</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/merritt-deth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/merritt-deth/</guid>
      <description>Merritt Deth is a New York-based artist and designer who makes meshy, stretchy, deconstructed tops for Café Forgot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>martina-cox</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/martina-cox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/martina-cox/</guid>
      <description>Café Forgot found Martina Cox’s thesis work on Instagram soon after she graduated from Cooper Union, and, when they contacted her, she’d never sold her clothing in a store. She has since become a Café Forgot mainstay with her signature “window tops” which are shirts with clear plastic panels smack-dab over the breast, some of which feature movable curtains or miniature flower boxes to open and close as the wearer desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maroske-peech</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/maroske-peech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/maroske-peech/</guid>
      <description>Maroske Peech is a collaboration between Australians, Elisa Keeler and Jordan Conder. The duo makes stunning pieces such as mesh high-rise leotards and silk shirts with buttons made from bread covered in enamel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>marland-backus</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/marland-backus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/marland-backus/</guid>
      <description>Marland Backus is a New York-based jewelry and furniture designer. She works with unexpected contrasting materials such as concrete, rubber, and human hair. Having grown up with Lucy and Vita, she works closely with Café Forgot and has helped design their spaces with custom furniture and displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liv-ryan</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-ryan/</guid>
      <description>Liv Ryan is based in Brooklyn, New York. Ryan’s garments are sculptural and geometric in form, riffing off street and workwear styles. Ryan also makes calamari-shaped earrings and sucked candy- shaped rounded earrings in cream colored glazed ceramic forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lou-dallas</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/lou-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/lou-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Lou Dallas was created by Raffaella Hanley in 2017. It is comprised of majority deadstock or recycled materials, and features loomed knits, embroidery, and embellishments done by hand. The fashion line evokes the baroque grandeur of the past and youthful splendor of present day New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kristin-mallison</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kristin-mallison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kristin-mallison/</guid>
      <description>Kristin Mallison is inspired by materials becoming something that they were never supposed to be. She fashions skirts and tops from old couch cushions, table runners and small donated needlepoint throw pillows. While the material is from the past, the cut and the style is from the future, and Mallison’s clothes become a contemporary synthesis of these two chronologies that is of the now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kira-scirbin</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kira-scirbin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kira-scirbin/</guid>
      <description>Kira Scirbin is a Chicago-based visual artist who turns second hand garments, hand bags, and chokers into canvases for her paintings and embroideries. Her work has a punk DIY aesthetic. Like her artwork, her designs often feature abstract, haunting paintings paired with commonplace words such as “earth” and “adult.” These words are given a new dimension once worn upon the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kahle</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kahle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kahle/</guid>
      <description>KAHLE, unadorned or bare in German, is a women&amp;rsquo;s luxury clothing brand based in Brooklyn, New York. Mary Kahle works out of her Greenpoint studio making sustainable clothing for women of all ages, shapes, and sizes. Her line of clothes is remarkably versatile and functional: Each garment can be worn in many ways depending on how it is tied or whether the wearer sports it upside down or inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jrat</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jrat/</guid>
      <description>JRAT is Janelle Rabbott, a Pacific Northwest native and Parsons School of Design graduate. She works exclusively in the “zero waste design methodology” ensuring that no waste is produced in the making of her products. Her work extends from sculpture, textiles, clothing, illustration, written words, to movement and dance. Her Café Forgot clothing features wide-cut pant legs and wrap-around tops and dresses that give license to vigorous movement, and her signature gray and fawn-colored textiles that are softened with frills and flower patterned overlays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jessica-butler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jessica-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jessica-butler/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Butler is a New York-based visual artist, poet, and photo editor at Artforum magazine. Butler cuts up old issues of Sassy mag to spell out sweet ransom notes, which she applies to chokers. She also makes necklaces out of collaged photos of fairytale forests or spooky caves and children’s knick-knacks like plastic frogs and spiders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>helenamanzano</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/helenamanzano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/helenamanzano/</guid>
      <description>HELENAMANZANO is a ready-to-wear line based in London. Manzano critiques the waste produced by the fashion industry through repurposing and recycling materials to create garments that reference the natural world. From a distance, her pieces often appear to be one-piece solid-colored constructions, yet, up close, they reveal themselves to be layered patterned fabrics overlaid with taupe, tan or black panels with unfinished, wispy edges and ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gauntlett-cheng</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gauntlett-cheng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gauntlett-cheng/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York, Esther Gauntlett and Jenny Cheng make clothes that reflect their realities and surroundings, exploring themes such as, adolescence and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>francesca-longo</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/francesca-longo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/francesca-longo/</guid>
      <description>Francesca Longo is a designer and illustrator born and raised in Brooklyn. Whether working in satin, silk or vinyl, she uses color, portraiture and volume to foster an aesthetic that projects new, radical notions of femininity. She loves Café Forgot because she believes firmly in the slow, but novel pace of fashion that we engender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>femail</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/femail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/femail/</guid>
      <description>FEMAIL is the brainchild of Parsons graduates Janelle Abbott and Camilla Carper. After college, they moved to Seattle and Los Angeles respectively, but sought to keep their friendship and collaboration alive from afar by mailing garments and collage back and forth to one another. For FEMAIL, no garment is finished, but is always growing and expanding as more mementos and fragments are added to create new ideas about fashion in function and form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>edie</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/edie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/edie/</guid>
      <description>EDIE is the work of our longtime friend, Edie Hanly. Her line is inspired by her father’s eclectic collection of gingham, plaid, and seersucker suits. Her green and white checkered pants are Café favorites as are her cosy slouch jackets. Best of all, her pieces are super flattering on every body type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delicate-porcelain</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/delicate-porcelain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/delicate-porcelain/</guid>
      <description>Delicate Porcelain is the collaborative project of musician Lila Gold and Josue Hurst. They tie-dye t-shirts and jeans and screen print psychedelic mushroom designs that read “mind, body, spirit, emotion.” Delicate Porcelain also creates nostalgic beaded jewelry that read “Be Kind” or “High in the Sky.” Lila Gold became involved with Café Forgot when she visited the shop, and since that meeting, she has collaborated with us many times and modeled for our editorial campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cm-carney</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/cm-carney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/cm-carney/</guid>
      <description>CM Carney creates wearables for videoed or live performances, which focus on abstract, aestheticized characters and narratives. At Café Forgot, CM Carney’s quilted body coverings and translucent extra long-sleeved crop tops become sculptural relics of past performances while taking on a new, utilitarian purpose as wearable clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>claire-mckinney</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/claire-mckinney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/claire-mckinney/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York and a graduate of Pratt Institute, Claire Mckinney’s one-of-a-kind garments explore materiality through construction and/ or collage. Some pieces deconstruct the “uniforms” of conformity: blue jeans, bomber jackets, work shoes and cotton blouses and rework them into new forms through elimination, reconfiguration and addition of color and materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>christie-keshet</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/christie-keshet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/christie-keshet/</guid>
      <description>Christie Keshet is a South African visual artist living in New York. Working primarily in watercolors, she’s drawn to the way the colors play once set free on paper. Often of figurative female forms and with a deceptively light touch, her work is simply beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>carolyn-killcoyne-voyta</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/carolyn-killcoyne-voyta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/carolyn-killcoyne-voyta/</guid>
      <description>Carolyn Killcoyne Voyta draws inspiration from nostalgic play clothes, combining soft cottons and gingham with plaids, tartans and stripes to make bikinis, tops with tie waists, skirts and dresses that shouldn’t work pattern-wise, yet do, and brilliantly! All her garments are made in the US using fabric from repurposed clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>by-tyler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/by-tyler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/by-tyler/</guid>
      <description>By Tyler, founded by New York-based designer, Tyler McGillivary, is a line of clothing to wiggle in. Her clothing, whether gauzy, flapjack-sized multicolored circles stitched together to make a top that dances before the eyes, or black, sheer, dresses punctuated by snake-like black twine that weaves around the wearers body, By Tyler will not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bror-august</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/bror-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/bror-august/</guid>
      <description>Norwegian line, Bror August, defies all expectations of what is wearable by designing clothes that may appear to be upside down, inside out, back to front, just seams punctuated with open spaces and sometimes all the above, yet everything he makes sits perfectly on the human form and feels seamlessly comfortable to the wearer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brie-moreno</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/brie-moreno/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 23:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/brie-moreno/</guid>
      <description>London-based illustrator, Brie Moreno, makes jewelry for Café Forgot. Her sparkly resin rings, replete with rosettes and glitter, have a girly, childish quality which is also present in her drawing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>balin</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/balin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 23:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/balin/</guid>
      <description>Founded by Jenny Balin Sonnenberg in 2018, Balin is a line of hand-sewn, hand-dyed, and bleached t-shirts superimposed with thought- provoking word play such as “Just Ice/ Justice” or “Please sure/ Pleasure.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>autobody</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/autobody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/autobody/</guid>
      <description>Autobody is a vintage inspired pants label created in 2014 by New Yorker and Pratt graduate, Cassie Goodman. Insanely comfortable, the pants have high waists and come in fly-off-the-shelves materials such as corduroy, pinstripe and vinyl. Best of all, the line is flattering on bodies of all shapes and sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>designers</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 08:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>info</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/info/</guid>
      <description>We (Vita Haas and Lucy Weisner) have been friends since high school in Brooklyn, New York. We attended college together where we talked incessantly about working on collaborative fashion projects.
When we moved back to New York after college, we conceived Café Forgot. We were inspired by the many friends who were making incredible clothes and accessories yet did not have an outlet for their work here. Our goal was to create a dynamic space to show and share truly interesting fashion and to hold special events to introduce these designers to a wider community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>anna-pierce</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/anna-pierce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/anna-pierce/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York and a graduate of the Rhode Island School of Design, Anna Pierce’s references range from Victorian England to nostalgic childhood arts and crafts. Among other things, Pierce has produced jewelry from pasta, and corsets, chokers and bracelets of gingham and velvet, often adding details such as chains, charms, hearts and grommets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>annabell-p-lee</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/annabell-p-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/annabell-p-lee/</guid>
      <description>Based in Los Angeles, Annabell P Lee makes paintings, textiles, and clothing inspired by the materiality of color in vintage melamine and PVC. Lee hand dyes chunky checkerboard patterns and abstract designs in fire-engine red and navy blue on denim jackets, wrap tops, and rough-hewn lace-up grommet corsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alterita</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alterita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alterita/</guid>
      <description>Layla Alter launched her jewelry line, Alterita, in 2018 with translucent ruby-red fruits, peppers and cowrie shells dangling from delicate hoops, necklaces and anklets. Her work is inspired by her upbringing when dreaded winter days in New York were spent dreaming of the ocean and yearning for summer’s first swim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alexa-stark</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alexa-stark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alexa-stark/</guid>
      <description>Based in Portland, Alexa Stark’s clothing reflects our complex age in which the designer and the wearer must balance the practical and the spectacle. Stark seeks to unify form, function and material using processes and production methods that adhere to sustainability and healthy work standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>picture_room</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/picture_room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/picture_room/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Lila Gold, Maya Laner, Rosy Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>165_duane_st</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/165_duane_st/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/165_duane_st/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Sara Grace Powell, Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Sara Grace Powell, Kat da Silva, Sabrina Fuentes, Daniela Lalita, Lulu Bonfils, Maggie Lee, Maia Ruth Lee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/temporary-wine-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/temporary-wine-bar/</guid>
      <description>Hosted by Jzuj – the collaborative cooking project of graphic designer, Owen Dodd and chef Nicholas Sewitz, the temporary wine bar spanned two evenings, providing a selection of snacks paired with natural wines. On the second night of the wine bar, opera soprano, Charlotte Jackson, provided live accompaniment, performing selected arias from the 17th-20th centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>archive</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 21:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/comedy-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/comedy-show/</guid>
      <description>Organized and curated in collaboration with friend and comedian Ruby McCollister, The Night You&amp;rsquo;ve Been Waiting For, featured performances by five comedic acts: Leah Hennessey and Emily Allan, Larry Owens, Peter Smith, Amy Zimmer, and Ruby McCollister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>170a_sufflolk_st_pt2</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_suffolk_st_pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 20:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_suffolk_st_pt2/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Katerina Tannenbaum, Erika Spring, Zoe Elise Bullock, Paulena Lynch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mirth_studio</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/mirth_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/mirth_studio/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Hayett McCarthy, Briar McQuilkin, Bobbi Menuez, Lida Fox, Adinah Dancyger, Paris Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>170a_sufflolk_st_pt1</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_sufflolk_st_pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 20:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_sufflolk_st_pt1/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Christian DeFonte. Model: Marland Backus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>