<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Designers on Café Forgot</title>
    <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Designers on Café Forgot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 19:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cafeforgot.com/designers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>official-rebrand</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/official-rebrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 19:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/official-rebrand/</guid>
      <description>Official Rebrand revives clothing that has been discarded, breathing new life into “waste”. Through painting and other alterations, non-binary designer MI Leggett&amp;rsquo;s “rebranding” proposes a sustainable alternative to competitive consumption. The transformation of these pieces also reflect the fluidity of identity, dissociating garments from gendered categories, reintroducing them without arbitrary social constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aiyana-jaffe</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/aiyana-jaffe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/aiyana-jaffe/</guid>
      <description>Aiyana Jaffe, a RISD graduate based in NY, designs and handcrafts fine jewelry using traditional silversmithing techniques paired with locally sourced vintage components. Exploring jewelry as a language of confidence, she finds nuance in bold forms allowing the wearer to feel both poised and causal. Aiyana celebrates the rare warmth of the hand made and the satisfaction of investing in new classics, made to last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>camille-beinhorn</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/camille-beinhorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/camille-beinhorn/</guid>
      <description>Camille Beinhorn is a classically trained jeweler based in Brooklyn, NY. She creates distinctive pieces with precious materials to activate and adorn the body. Her one of a kind pieces feature rare and unusual cuts of gemstones in alluring combinations and a lush palette. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mila-sullivan</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mila-sullivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 17:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mila-sullivan/</guid>
      <description>Mila Sullivan is a ready-to-wear line based in Brooklyn, New York, which was founded by three Pratt Institute graduates. Mila Sullivan creates one-of-a-kind pieces, often deconstructing and layering vintage home-goods fabrics to create eclectic and nostalgic garments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>paid-actor</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/paid-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 20:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/paid-actor/</guid>
      <description>Paid Actor is the wearable extension of Dessislava Terzieva&amp;rsquo;s fine art practice which is rooted in collage and found object sculpture. Terzeiva explores fashion as a form of communication, the body as a canvas, and the wearer as the messenger. Each piece has it&amp;rsquo;s own unique narrative, whether it is in relation to the imagery/artwork featured on it, or the story behind the material(s) being used. Holistically, the very existence of these one-of-a-kind garments is a statement against fast fashion, trend worship and a look-alike culture fostered by social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zelda-passini</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zelda-passini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zelda-passini/</guid>
      <description>Zelda Passini is a jewelry designer based in Paris. Passini’s work is inspired by postmodern aesthetics, art-deco design and industrial objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tropical-rob</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tropical-rob/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tropical-rob/</guid>
      <description>Tropical Rob serves the hottest fashions du jour. Founded by Robert Hurlbut in 2015, the Los Angeles based line features digital prints of his hand-painted textile designs. TR is a fantasy interpretation of his youth in California, London and at RISD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teva-livne</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/teva-livne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/teva-livne/</guid>
      <description>Teva Livne is a sculptor and artist living in New York. She works with clay, paint and glitter to create an unraveling dream world of shapes, mystery animals, friendship, fantasy and cat charms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>susannah-cutler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susannah-cutler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susannah-cutler/</guid>
      <description>Susannah Cutler is a folk musician and Brooklyn-based textile designer. Her thesis project caught the attention of Café Forgot in the summer of 2018. Her fabrics feature her watercolor drawings of flowers and kittens, which she fashions into breezy sleeveless dresses and crop tops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sophie-andes-gascon</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sophie-andes-gascon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sophie-andes-gascon/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn, New York-based designer Sophie Andes-Gascon produces hand-constructed garments, each with its own story. Andes-Gascon recycles worn fabrics such as dish rags or worker’s uniforms and transforms them into beautiful beaded creations with meticulous attention to detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sara-brooks</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sara-brooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sara-brooks/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn based Sara Brooks makes eclectic clothes that manage to combine a sporty look plus western embellishment and structure with notes of dated sci-fi. She artfully uses seams and fasteners to give shape to her hand-dyed creative creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>poche</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/poche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/poche/</guid>
      <description>Based in Los Angeles, Poche is an atelier that investigates the nuances and constructions of everyday wear and living. They explore the essence of relationships with dress, furnishings and homeware within the context of everyday life. Each piece is hand sewn or outsourced in small batches in Los Angeles as a means of demassification. Poche often uses dead-stock and recycled fabric to create distinctive season-less few-offs. Poche is for everyday use and everyday wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>piera-bochner</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/piera-bochner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/piera-bochner/</guid>
      <description>Piera Bochner is an artist and designer based in Brooklyn, New York, and a long-time friend of Vita and Lucy. Bochner’s candle project comes from a love of wax as a material and a desire to investigate how wicks, wax, and flames can travel down unconventional paths. As they burn, the colorful wax candles cast from romanesco broccoli and bitter melons become ever-changing sculptural forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pearle-knits</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/pearle-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/pearle-knits/</guid>
      <description>Pearle Knits, is a New York-based label by designer Michaela Pearle from Vancouver, Canada. Her knitwear explores the traditional notions behind women and crafts, and revels in the nostalgia of handmade clothing. Each piece is meticulously handcrafted on a knitting machine in New York and features super-soft, stretchy cotton yarn sourced from mills in Canada and the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onea</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/onea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/onea/</guid>
      <description>The work of New York based artist, Onea Engel-Bradley, asks us to think critically about the ways in which ‘strong’ women are characterized in fashion. Rejecting the ‘power suit,’ her line ranges from sheer romantic elastane dresses to tailored, menswear-inspired linen trousers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nicole-van-vuuren</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/nicole-van-vuuren/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/nicole-van-vuuren/</guid>
      <description>Nicole Van Vuuren is an Auckland, New Zealand based designer exploring fashion through mundane interactions between the body, cloth and garments. After graduating from the fashion program at RMIT University in Melbourne, Australia, she moved to New York, to work in the Eckhaus Latta studio where she and began her current ‘scrap t shirt’ project. Using small pieces of fabric and off-cuts she hand cuts and stitches her enigmatic paneled shirts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>molly-rose-lieberman</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/molly-rose-lieberman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/molly-rose-lieberman/</guid>
      <description>Molly Rose Lieberman is a painter living in Brooklyn, New York. Using found materials, Molly makes wearable objects available at Café Forgot. She also makes small paintings and drawings which have been featured at the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>merritt-meacham</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/merritt-deth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/merritt-deth/</guid>
      <description>Merritt Meacham&amp;rsquo;s work is trapped between the destruction of the fancied playful and the technical tedium of the body. Merritt works with paint, dye, wine, plastic and deadstock fabric to make stretchy tops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>martina-cox</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/martina-cox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/martina-cox/</guid>
      <description>Café Forgot found Martina Cox’s thesis work on Instagram soon after she graduated from Cooper Union, and, when they contacted her, she’d never sold her clothing in a store. She has since become a Café Forgot mainstay with her signature “window tops” which are shirts with clear plastic panels smack-dab over the breast, some of which feature movable curtains or miniature flower boxes to open and close as the wearer desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maroske-peech</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/maroske-peech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/maroske-peech/</guid>
      <description>Maroske Peech is a collaboration between Australians, Elisa Keeler and Jordan Conder. The duo makes stunning pieces such as mesh high-rise leotards and silk shirts with buttons made from bread covered in enamel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>marland-backus</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/marland-backus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/marland-backus/</guid>
      <description>Marland Backus is a New York-based jewelry and furniture designer. She works with unexpected contrasting materials such as concrete, rubber, and human hair. Having grown up with Lucy and Vita, she works closely with Café Forgot and has helped design their spaces with custom furniture and displays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liv-ryan</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-ryan/</guid>
      <description>Liv Ryan is based in Brooklyn, New York. Ryan’s garments are sculptural and geometric in form, riffing off street and workwear styles. Ryan also makes calamari-shaped earrings and sucked candy- shaped rounded earrings in cream colored glazed ceramic forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lou-dallas</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/lou-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/lou-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Lou Dallas was created by Raffaella Hanley in 2017. Hanley custom-sews recycled and deadstock materials, and dyes each garment by hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kristin-mallison</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kristin-mallison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kristin-mallison/</guid>
      <description>Kristin Mallison is inspired by materials becoming something that they were never supposed to be. She fashions skirts and tops from old couch cushions, table runners and small donated needlepoint throw pillows. While the material is from the past, the cut and the style is from the future, and Mallison’s clothes become a contemporary synthesis of these two chronologies that is of the now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kira-scerbin </title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kira-scirbin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kira-scirbin/</guid>
      <description>Kira Scirbin is a Chicago-based visual artist who makes garments, hand bags, and chokers that are used as canvases for her paintings and embroideries. Her work has a punk DIY aesthetic and often features abstract, haunting paintings paired with commonplace words such as “earth” and “adult.” These words are given a new dimension once worn upon the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kahle</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kahle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kahle/</guid>
      <description>KAHLE, unadorned or bare in German, is a women&amp;rsquo;s luxury clothing brand based in Brooklyn, New York. Mary Kahle works out of her Greenpoint studio making sustainable clothing for women of all ages, shapes, and sizes. Her line of clothes is remarkably versatile and functional: Each garment can be worn in many ways depending on how it is tied or whether the wearer sports it upside down or inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jrat</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jrat/</guid>
      <description>JRAT is Janelle Rabbott, a Pacific Northwest native and Parsons School of Design graduate. She works exclusively in the “zero waste design methodology” ensuring that no waste is produced in the making of her products. Her work extends from sculpture, textiles, clothing, illustration, written words, to movement and dance. Her Café Forgot clothing features wide-cut pant legs and wrap-around tops and dresses that give license to vigorous movement, and her signature gray and fawn-colored textiles that are softened with frills and flower patterned overlays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jessica-butler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jessica-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/jessica-butler/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Butler is a New York-based visual artist, poet, and photo editor at Artforum magazine. Butler cuts up old issues of Sassy mag to spell out sweet ransom notes, which she applies to chokers. She also makes necklaces out of collaged photos of fairytale forests or spooky caves and children’s knick-knacks like plastic frogs and spiders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>helenamanzano</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/helenamanzano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/helenamanzano/</guid>
      <description>HELENAMANZANO is a ready-to-wear line based in London. Manzano critiques the waste produced by the fashion industry through repurposing and recycling materials to create garments that reference the natural world. From a distance, her pieces often appear to be one-piece solid-colored constructions, yet, up close, they reveal themselves to be layered patterned fabrics overlaid with taupe, tan or black panels with unfinished, wispy edges and ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gauntlett-cheng</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gauntlett-cheng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gauntlett-cheng/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York, Esther Gauntlett and Jenny Cheng make clothes that reflect their realities and surroundings, exploring themes such as, adolescence and sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>francesca-longo</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/francesca-longo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/francesca-longo/</guid>
      <description>Francesca Longo is a designer and illustrator born and raised in Brooklyn. Whether working in satin, silk or vinyl, she uses color, portraiture and volume to foster an aesthetic that projects new, radical notions of femininity. She loves Café Forgot because she believes firmly in the slow, but novel pace of fashion that we engender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>femail</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/femail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/femail/</guid>
      <description>FEMAIL is the brainchild of Parsons graduates Janelle Abbott and Camilla Carper. After college, they moved to Seattle and Los Angeles respectively, but sought to keep their friendship and collaboration alive from afar by mailing garments and collage back and forth to one another. For FEMAIL, no garment is finished, but is always growing and expanding as more mementos and fragments are added to create new ideas about fashion in function and form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>edie</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/edie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/edie/</guid>
      <description>EDIE is the work of our longtime friend, Edie Hanly. Her line is inspired by her father’s eclectic collection of gingham, plaid, and seersucker suits. Her green and white checkered pants are Café favorites as are her cosy slouch jackets. Best of all, her pieces are super flattering on every body type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delicate-porcelain</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/delicate-porcelain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/delicate-porcelain/</guid>
      <description>Delicate Porcelain is the collaborative project of musician Lila Gold and Josue Hurst. They tie-dye t-shirts and jeans and screen print psychedelic mushroom designs that read “mind, body, spirit, emotion.” Delicate Porcelain also creates nostalgic beaded jewelry that read “Be Kind” or “High in the Sky.” Lila Gold became involved with Café Forgot when she visited the shop, and since that meeting, she has collaborated with us many times and modeled for our editorial campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cm-carney</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/cm-carney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/cm-carney/</guid>
      <description>CM Carney creates wearables for videoed or live performances, which focus on abstract, aestheticized characters and narratives. At Café Forgot, CM Carney’s quilted body coverings and translucent extra long-sleeved crop tops become sculptural relics of past performances while taking on a new, utilitarian purpose as wearable clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>claire-mckinney</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/claire-mckinney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 19:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/claire-mckinney/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York and a graduate of Pratt Institute, Claire Mckinney’s one-of-a-kind garments explore materiality through construction and/ or collage. Some pieces deconstruct the “uniforms” of conformity: blue jeans, bomber jackets, work shoes and cotton blouses and rework them into new forms through elimination, reconfiguration and addition of color and materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>christie-keshet</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/christie-keshet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/christie-keshet/</guid>
      <description>Christie Keshet is a South African visual artist living in New York. Working primarily in watercolors, she’s drawn to the way the colors play once set free on paper. Often of figurative female forms and with a deceptively light touch, her work is simply beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>carolyn-killcoyne-voyta</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/carolyn-killcoyne-voyta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/carolyn-killcoyne-voyta/</guid>
      <description>Carolyn Killcoyne Voyta draws inspiration from nostalgic play clothes, combining soft cottons and gingham with plaids, tartans and stripes to make bikinis, tops with tie waists, skirts and dresses that shouldn’t work pattern-wise, yet do, and brilliantly! All her garments are made in the US using fabric from repurposed clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>by-tyler</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/by-tyler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/by-tyler/</guid>
      <description>By Tyler, founded by New York-based designer, Tyler McGillivary, is a line of clothing to wiggle in. Her clothing, whether gauzy, flapjack-sized multicolored circles stitched together to make a top that dances before the eyes, or black, sheer, dresses punctuated by snake-like black twine that weaves around the wearers body, By Tyler will not be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bror-august</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/bror-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/bror-august/</guid>
      <description>Norwegian line, Bror August, defies all expectations of what is wearable by designing clothes that may appear to be upside down, inside out, back to front, just seams punctuated with open spaces and sometimes all the above, yet everything he makes sits perfectly on the human form and feels seamlessly comfortable to the wearer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brie-moreno</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/brie-moreno/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 23:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/brie-moreno/</guid>
      <description>London-based illustrator, Brie Moreno, makes jewelry for Café Forgot. Her sparkly resin rings, replete with rosettes and glitter, have a girly, childish quality which is also present in her drawing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>balin</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/balin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 23:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/balin/</guid>
      <description>Founded by Jenny Balin Sonnenberg in 2018, Balin is a line of hand-sewn, hand-dyed, and bleached t-shirts superimposed with thought- provoking word play such as “Just Ice/ Justice” or “Please sure/ Pleasure.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>autobody</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/autobody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/autobody/</guid>
      <description>Autobody is a vintage inspired pants label created in 2014 by New Yorker and Pratt graduate, Cassie Goodman. Insanely comfortable, the pants have high waists and come in fly-off-the-shelves materials such as corduroy, pinstripe and vinyl. Best of all, the line is flattering on bodies of all shapes and sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>anna-pierce</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/anna-pierce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/anna-pierce/</guid>
      <description>Based in New York and a graduate of the Rhode Island School of Design, Anna Pierce’s references range from Victorian England to nostalgic childhood arts and crafts. Among other things, Pierce has produced jewelry from pasta, and corsets, chokers and bracelets of gingham and velvet, often adding details such as chains, charms, hearts and grommets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>annabell-p-lee</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/annabell-p-lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/annabell-p-lee/</guid>
      <description>Based in Los Angeles, Annabell P Lee makes paintings, textiles, and clothing inspired by the materiality of color in vintage melamine and PVC. Lee hand dyes chunky checkerboard patterns and abstract designs in fire-engine red and navy blue on denim jackets, wrap tops, and rough-hewn lace-up grommet corsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alterita</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alterita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alterita/</guid>
      <description>Layla Alter launched her jewelry line, Alterita, in 2018 with translucent ruby-red fruits, peppers and cowrie shells dangling from delicate hoops, necklaces and anklets. Her work is inspired by her upbringing when dreaded winter days in New York were spent dreaming of the ocean and yearning for summer’s first swim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alexa-stark</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alexa-stark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alexa-stark/</guid>
      <description>Based in Portland, Alexa Stark’s clothing reflects our complex age in which the designer and the wearer must balance the practical and the spectacle. Stark seeks to unify form, function and material using processes and production methods that adhere to sustainability and healthy work standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>69herbs</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/69herbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/69herbs/</guid>
      <description>69herbs is a New York-based apothecary and design project by Jade Marks. 69herbs aestheticizes a dream of collective healing by blending fantasy, faggotry, and folk herbalism. Herbal creations are handmade in Brooklyn with locally &amp;amp; sustainably grown plants whenever possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ali-bonfils</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/ali-bonfils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/ali-bonfils/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn based artist Ali Bonfils uses sculpy, repurposed gems, beads, and charms to make jewelry. Inspired by the decadence of victorian chokers and the handmade sentiment of friendship bracelets, her oven-baked adornments are made with love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>alice-lancaster</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alice-lancaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/alice-lancaster/</guid>
      <description>Alice Lancaster is an artist and animal rights activist living and working in New York City. Her colorful pieces are all secondhand and one of a kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>all-is-a-gentle-spring</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/all-is-a-gentle-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/all-is-a-gentle-spring/</guid>
      <description>all is a gentle spring is a clothing project founded in Melbourne, Australia. It offers thrashable basics and special-occasion dress-ups inspired by historic costume to add an element of fantasy to your everyday dress. The label generates non-seasonal collections, one-off recycled fabric garments, and small collaborative capsules with artists and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aurelia-cotton</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/aurelia-cotton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/aurelia-cotton/</guid>
      <description>Aurelia Cotton is a jewelry designer based in New York. After attending RISD for apparel design, she has been making jewelry for 10 years. Her latest collection is primarily focused on found objects, charms, and pieces salvaged from her childhood collaged into one-of-a-kind pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beepy-bella</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/beepy-bella/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/beepy-bella/</guid>
      <description>Beepy Bella is the jewelry and accessories line of artist, Isabella Lalonde. Handmade in her New York studio, Lalonde&amp;rsquo;s jewelry explores childhood, fantasy, and fairytales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blobbs</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/blobbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/blobbs/</guid>
      <description>Blobbs are one-of-a-kind miniature sculptures for the body handmade by Sofía Elias in Mexico City. These small-scale experiments contrast glitzy stones with inorganic materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>care-instructions</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/care-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/care-instructions/</guid>
      <description>Care Instructions is the clothing project of Brooklyn-based textile artist Anne Symons. Symons naturally dyes swaths of silk and celebrates them through environmental installation and movement-driven works called Windpuppets. She then repurposes the material and combines it with found vintage textiles to make clothes and other wearables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>caroline-david</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/caroline-david/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/caroline-david/</guid>
      <description>Caroline David is an artist currently living in Berlin. Her ceramic work for Café Forgot celebrates the power of fostering life and growth in the everyday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>crying-clover-candles</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/crying-clover-candles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/crying-clover-candles/</guid>
      <description>Crying clover candles is the partnership between two artists - Patrick Walsh (aka JPW3) and Sara Gernsbacher. It was born out of experimentations with sculptural forms. Every crying clover candle is a unique artwork made from reclaimed wax with hand drawn oil pastel transfers. No two are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>demuerte</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/demuerte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/demuerte/</guid>
      <description>demuerte is a garment label designed by Joshua Jenkins exploring American identities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>docwang</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/docwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/docwang/</guid>
      <description>DOC.WANG is the collaborative line of Ben Doctor and Sophie Wang that focuses on maximalist wearables and cute accessories. Based in Providence, Rhode Island, Doctor and Wang spend their days quilting, dyeing, stuffing, painting and beading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>emily-fitzpatrick</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emily-fitzpatrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emily-fitzpatrick/</guid>
      <description>Emily Fitzpatrick is an artist based in New York. Her ceramic forms are built by hand using traditional methods. Each piece uniquely expresses an appreciation for nature and a sentimentality for the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>emilydawnlong</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emilydawnlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emilydawnlong/</guid>
      <description>EMILYDAWNLONG is an eponymous New York-based brand specializing in textile design and up-cycled material. The multidisciplinary artist creates collections inspired by pieces in her personal archive of treasures she has collected for clients from vintage vendors and flea markets all over the world. Emily works as a stylist and creative consultant on projects ranging from fashion editorial and ceramics to furniture design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>emma-pryde</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emma-pryde/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/emma-pryde/</guid>
      <description>Emma Pryde is a visual artist who works primarily with ceramic and laser cut acrylic. Her work explores fantasy, art history and entertainment media. Her sculptures and jewelry are inspired by plastic toys and religious ephemera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fior-di-latte</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/fior-di-latte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/fior-di-latte/</guid>
      <description>Carla Cassataro is an artist and designer based in New York. Her handmade designs reflect her fascination with creating texture from stitching techniques. Fior di Latte, which translates to flower of milk, is a combination of influence from her Sicilian roots and New York DNA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flower-names</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/flower-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/flower-names/</guid>
      <description>FLOWER NAMES is naturally-dyed clothing and accessories for earthlings. Thrifted fabric is used to make one of a kind pieces, while other items are made in teeny tiny batches. Many colors are only available seasonally and some colors only appear once. Everything is hand-dyed and sewn by Jasmine Cindy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gabe-gordon</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gabe-gordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/gabe-gordon/</guid>
      <description>Gabe Gordon is a New York based designer and artist currently studying at the Rhode Island School of Design. He makes knitwear exploring themes of grief and sexuality and likes looking at stains, rainbows, and smiley faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>garbage-core</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/garbage-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/garbage-core/</guid>
      <description>Garbage Core is a project by Milan based designer Giudetta Tanzi. Tanzi makes handmade and one-of-a-kind garments and accessories out of second hand clothing from street markets, friends, and family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>goodwitch</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/goodwitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/goodwitch/</guid>
      <description>GOODWITCH makes herbal formulas for healing using plants and cannabis sustainably grown on local farms and foraged in the Hudson Valley. All bottles and packaging are made in limited edition runs recently featuring the work of Gabrielle Rosenstein and Caroline David. Medicine for everyone, inspired by life with chronic pain and disorderly moods. TRUST BODY SIGNALS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hanan-sharifa</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/hanan-sharifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/hanan-sharifa/</guid>
      <description>Hanan Sharifa is a Brooklyn based artist working in a variety of materials and fabrics including re-purposed denim, mesh, jersey, and satin. In Arabic, Hanan means &amp;ldquo;tender&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;compassionate&amp;rdquo; , she includes her name on many of her garments in an effort to push against the English language as a global standard. Through this simple act, she is validating not only the Arabic language, but Muslim culture, and expression. Her garments often reveal unseen parts of the body as a way to reimagine the history of fabric into an intersectional contemporary narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>joanna-fields</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/joanna-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/joanna-fields/</guid>
      <description>Joanna Fields is an artist living in New York. Her work evokes stoner clown psychedelia, simultaneously adorable and grotesque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>karla-laidlaw</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/karla-laidlaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/karla-laidlaw/</guid>
      <description>Karla Laidlaw is a Melbourne based designer who creates one-off pieces and small runs of her garments. All garments are repurposed and reworked—dyed, bleached, painted, and sewn by hand. The designs are influenced by people who know who they are and use their personal style to express themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>krystal-paniagua</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/krystal-paniagua/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/krystal-paniagua/</guid>
      <description>Krystal Paniagua is a knitwear designer native to Puerto Rico. Her work focuses on the communities that surround her which serve as the foundation for her textiles and garments. Through her garments she envisions her idea of collectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kunst</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/kunst/</guid>
      <description>Kunst curates a selection of handmade and vintage clothing and accessories. Focused on recycled materials, unique and imaginative designs, Kunst’s handmade pieces and vintage selections are made for those who are conscious and concerned about the environmental issues that the fashion industry creates. Kunst is a creative solution to the second-largest source of pollution: textile waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liv-by-liv</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-by-liv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/liv-by-liv/</guid>
      <description>Started by a preschool teacher, LivByLiv is made to take you from whatever you may be doing by day to whatever you may be doing at night, in comfort and style. Each sustainable piece is hand made in Liv’s Brooklyn studio using dead-stock recycled fabric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>louise-lyngh-bjerregaard</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/louise-lyngh-bjerregaard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/louise-lyngh-bjerregaard/</guid>
      <description>Louise Lyngh Bjerregaard is based in Copenhagen and works mainly in experimental, gender-fluid knitwear made out of scrap yarns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>m-hiramatsu</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/m-hiramatsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/m-hiramatsu/</guid>
      <description>M. Hiramatsu is a Tokyo based brand exploring traditional and hand-made practices, such as embroidery and crocheting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mgn</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/mgn/</guid>
      <description>MGN is a sculptural jewellery label founded by Megan Baker in Melbourne, Australia. Her collections are meditations on the beauty and imperfections of precious metals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>number-sixteen</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/number-sixteen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/number-sixteen/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2018, number sixteen is a Montreal-based label created by Kate McConnan. Informed by her education in textile arts and a family history of artisanship, she explores concepts of craft and womanhood to subvert stereotypes of feminine aesthetics and trends in fashion. Using carefully selected natural materials, each piece is handmade by Kate in her studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oma</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/oma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/oma/</guid>
      <description>OMA Jewelry was conceived by Heather David as a solution to sculpture making in small spaces. The name OMA is an acronym for “one more again.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>physical-affection</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/physical-affection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/physical-affection/</guid>
      <description>Physical Affection is the Brooklyn based accessories label created by self taught designer and artist Angela Vitello. She&amp;rsquo;s concerned with joyfulness and pleasure and her designs reflect a childlike sense of wonder and beauty. She aims to glorify the ethos of crafting and low culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rebekah-bide</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/rebekah-bide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/rebekah-bide/</guid>
      <description>Rebekah Bide is an Australian artist living in London. She makes sculptures and wearable pieces that are handcrafted using a combination of contemporary and archaic techniques, such as gilding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>retsiort-esile</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/retsiort-esile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/retsiort-esile/</guid>
      <description>Retsiort Esile is a Toronto-based label by designer Elise Troister. The driving aesthetic is utility wear, kitsch nostalgia, and 1980s silhouettes. With sustainability in mind, the designs use deadstock fabric and found materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>room-shop</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/room-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/room-shop/</guid>
      <description>Room Shop started out as a vintage pop-up shop in the back bedroom of Shelly Horst and Dryw Scully’s Philadelphia row home. It has evolved into a sustainable line of apparel and accessories made from remnant, deadstock and overstock materials. Most famous for their Cloud Scrunchie, they are now delving into apparel design, keeping their commitment to sustainable design and responsible production. Room Shop’s products are made in Philadelphia, PA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roseanne-johnson</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/roseanne-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/roseanne-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Roseanne Johnson is an artist from the Columbia River Gorge, living in Chicago. Her hand-worked clothing seeks the ruination of productivity and respectability. She accumulates and arranges fragments in improvised recipes as a way of questioning and pulling at wild threads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>runny-babbit</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/runny-babbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/runny-babbit/</guid>
      <description>Runny Babbit is Los Angeles based clothing designer Jane Harris. Through a nostalgic lens, Harris creates in her home studio with repurposed materials. Her pieces offer thoughtful and romantic details, often playing with visibility through shape, transparency, and layering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shii-said</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/shii-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/shii-said/</guid>
      <description>Shii Said is a ready-to-wear line by designer, Shi Fan, inspired by women’s lingerie silhouettes and construction techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so-far</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/so-far/</guid>
      <description>So Far is a womenswear label made in NYC by Sophia Fish. Originally designed in Marfa, Texas, So Far takes inspiration from the geometry of the high desert and the relationship these shapes have to the body. Each collection is made using only recycled, dead stock, and sustainable fabrics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sparkle-diva</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sparkle-diva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/sparkle-diva/</guid>
      <description>Sparkle Diva believes feathers are casual, rhinestones are mandatory, and life is best viewed through bedazzled, rose colored glasses. Whether tanning on Panama City Beach or shopping on the Champs-Élysées, there is a Sparkle Diva in all of us. Sparkle Diva&amp;rsquo;s accessories collection is imagined in Brooklyn, NY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>susan-alexandra</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susan-alexandra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/susan-alexandra/</guid>
      <description>Susan Alexandra is dedicated to bringing joy and sparkle to everyday life. Each item is made by hand in NYC, creating a myriad of sustainable jobs. Every piece is intended to be a source of happy joyful moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tashi-fay</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tashi-fay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/tashi-fay/</guid>
      <description>TASHi FAY is an artist and designer based in Brooklyn, New York. Tashi collages Frankensteinian confections using materials such as vintage children’s nightgowns, her father’s old gingham button down and recycled dry cleaner bags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>timosassen</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/timosassen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/timosassen/</guid>
      <description>timosassen is a self-taught fashion designer and visual artist based in Antwerp and NYC. After years of experimenting in his living room atelier, Sassen founded his eponymous label in 2018, making simple, wearable, sexy pieces in unexpected cuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>under-the-rug</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/under-the-rug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/under-the-rug/</guid>
      <description>under.the.rug is name of artist/musician Abby Gallagher’s knitwear and clothing project. Gallagher makes one-of-a-kind pieces with sustainable materials for herself, her friends, and Café Forgot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>venicew</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/venicew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/venicew/</guid>
      <description>VeniceW is a land that orbits around mundane life, laziness, nothingness and time.
VeniceW is a destination for humans to slow down &amp;amp; take a good look at the boredom of life.
VeniceW is currently occupied by 2 types of citizens, Collections and Goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zak-syroka</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zak-syroka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zak-syroka/</guid>
      <description>Excited by uncontrollable outcomes, Zak Syroka makes use of fabric, dye, and other materials to create one-of-a-kind pieces for on and off the body. Zak lives and works in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zepherina</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zepherina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zepherina/</guid>
      <description>Designer Renea LaRiviere founded the concept in 2018 as an ode to her Great Grandmother Zepherina. A combined influence of familial photographs, stories, and heirlooms constructed her character of Zepherina. This narrative is illustrated in her collection of limited-edition silhouettes, crafted with premium textiles and one-of-a-kind details for a mysterious-yet-sophisticated look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zmsw</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zmsw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/designers/zmsw/</guid>
      <description>ZMSW is a swimwear line founded in New York by designer Zita Medvedova. Yearning for an idyllic past, Medvedova’s work takes inspiration from the beaches of São Paulo, 90s girl bands, and 20th century &amp;amp; early 2000s icons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>