<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on CAFÉ FORGOT</title>
    <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on CAFÉ FORGOT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://cafeforgot.com/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/heaven-i-stay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/heaven-i-stay/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/summer-reading-and-party-with-luke-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/summer-reading-and-party-with-luke-simon/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday July 15 we hosted a celebration and reading from “VENUS JUICE: When I Tried To Live in LA” by author and healer, Luke Simon.
ABOUT VENUS JUICE:
VENUS JUICE takes readers on a neo-nostalgic trip into the LA wellness scene of the late 2010s, a land of luxury juice, natural healing, and digital hookups. On the surface the City of Angels seems to hold the keys to all that Luke seeks—love, creativity and how to make it as an Instagram healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/29-ludlow-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/29-ludlow-st/</guid>
      <description>Opening party June 16, 6–8 PM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/40_w_27th_st/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/40_w_27th_st/</guid>
      <description>We are open by appointment two days per week on Thursday and Friday. To sign up for an appointment email info@cafeforgot.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/eau-de-parfum-no-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/eau-de-parfum-no-1/</guid>
      <description>Campaign by Monika Mogi with Marland Backus and Hanano Momose. Music by Tex Crick. Watch Here.
Click Here to Purchase. Eau de Parfum No 1 is developed in collaboration with Moscow based nose, Maria Golovina. Scent notes include pink peppercorn, dried rose, almond milk, and new stockings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/ceremony-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/ceremony-1/</guid>
      <description>Click the link to download our digital book in collaboration with Pratt Fashion class of 2020. DOWNLOAD HERE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/screen-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/screen-dreams/</guid>
      <description>In this moment of unprecedented isolation, when connection and community tend to be mediated by a screen, Café Forgot presented a night of stories, poems, and essays mediated by a screen with Bobbi Salvör Menuez, Coco Gordon Moore, Gideon Jacobs, Rebekah Campbell, Stepahanie LaCava, and Yves B. Golden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/side-effect-virtual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/side-effect-virtual/</guid>
      <description>Café Forgot in collaboration with Jade Forrest Marks and Cara Marie Piazza hosted a series of virtual workshops focused on healing and catharsis during the time of COVID-19.
Workshops included:
FOUND FLORA SCULPTURES with Fleurotica, PYSCHOPHARMACOLOGICAL MEDITATIONS with Gideon Jacobs, EMBODIED MOVEMENT WORKSHOP with Marisa Hall, BODYSPELL: Somatic Plant Meditation + Improvised Movement Session with GOODWITCH, INTRO TO HARM REDUCTION with Ripley Soprano, HERBS + ELIXIRS FOR RELATIONSHIPS with Suanny Upegui of Casa Finca, EDIBLE BEAUTY: CONVERSATION + DEMONSTRATION OF SPRING MEDICINALS with Antonia Perez, and VIRTUAL REIKI SESSIONS with lily bo shapiro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/virtual-breathwork-healing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/virtual-breathwork-healing/</guid>
      <description>In this virtual healing group, live on Zoom, Luke Simon led participants in a Breathwork journey to shake off restlessness and worry, and move forward with courage, creativity and trust.
Breathwork is an active meditation that takes you out of the mind and into feeling. The increased oxygen flow shifts your brain chemistry, helping old emotions to release and new understanding to dawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/fashion-meditation-with-luke-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/fashion-meditation-with-luke-simon/</guid>
      <description>A guided journey to ground yourself and open your intuition. Connect to the essence of your style with prompts to uncover the colors, textures and looks your spirit is craving. Uniting intuition with appreciation for life, we receive new visions for ourselves and the planet. Guided by Luke Simon with music by Deta Factor &amp;amp; Matthewdavid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/documentary-test-screnning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/documentary-test-screnning/</guid>
      <description>In light of the pandemic we wanted to share Cyrus Duff&amp;rsquo;s Untitled Café Forgot Documentary, which originally screened at Anthology Film Archives on February 24, 2020.
CLICK HERE TO WATCH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/627-e-6th-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/627-e-6th-st/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Tasmin Meyer Ersahin.
Models: Giannina Oteto, Kaia Jane Abraham, Ava Ferguson, Manon Macasaet, Lumia Nocito, Taylor Jeanne, Sadaf Nava, Dasha Nekrasova, Seashell Coker, Vera Bulder, Hannah Woldetsadik, Sabrina Fuentes, Kelly Zutrau.
Images co-produced with No Agency New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/side-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/side-effect/</guid>
      <description>Side Effect has been postponed due to COVID-19. Stay tuned for updates. If you already purchased tickets you will be contacted via email regarding refunds. Take care + stay safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/dream-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/dream-room/</guid>
      <description>Designer Renea LaRiviere founded the concept for her line in 2018 as an ode to her Great Grandmother Zepherina. A combined influence of familial photographs, stories, and heirlooms constructed her character of Zepherina. This narrative is illustrated in her collection of limited-edition silhouettes, crafted with premium textiles and one-of-a-kind details for a mysterious-yet-sophisticated look. This March, for A Narrative Room, Renea will create an immersive installation of found furniture, art objects, and one-of-a-kind garments, featuring work by Claudia Cruz, Daisy Chains, and Ty &amp;amp; Calla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/test-screnning-untitled-cafe-forgot-documetary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/test-screnning-untitled-cafe-forgot-documetary/</guid>
      <description>On February 24th, 2020, Café Forgot and No Agency New York hosted an intimate test screening at Anthology Film Archives of Cyrus Duff&amp;rsquo;s unfinished documentary on Cafe&amp;rsquo;s inception and journey from ephemeral pop-ups to a long-term East Village lease. Duff&amp;rsquo;s documentary also covers the collaboration and conflict between Café Forgot and No Agency New York on a recent shoot.
RSVP ONLY — rsvp@noagency.nyc
8 PM, Monday, February 24
ANTHOLOGY FILM ARCHIVES</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/breathwork-healing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/breathwork-healing/</guid>
      <description>Breathwork healing at Café Forgot (627 E 6th ST), lead by mystic, Luke Simon of Maha Rose addresses the energetic intensity of life in NYC. Breathwork is an active meditation that takes you out of the mind and into feeling. As you relax and let go, the increased oxygen flow rejuvenates your body and helps to open your heart.
Tickets</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/larrie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/larrie/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Christian DeFonte, Sasha Frolova.
Models: Yasmine Geurts, Vera Bulder, Christian DeFonte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/true-blue-eyeshadow-personal-trainer-sadie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/true-blue-eyeshadow-personal-trainer-sadie/</guid>
      <description>Larrie and Café Forgot were pleased to host a concert with True Blue, Eyeshadow, Personal Trainer, and Sadie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/becky-akinyode-in-conversation-with-martina-cox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/becky-akinyode-in-conversation-with-martina-cox/</guid>
      <description>Café Forgot founders Lucy Weisner and Vita Haas moderated a conversation between stylist Becky Akinyode and artist/designer Martina Cox. The discussion focused on the impact of limited edition and handmade clothing in their respective practices as well as utilizing second hand clothing as a visual and physical resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/marie-lea-lund-chakra-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/marie-lea-lund-chakra-survey/</guid>
      <description>Marie Lea Lund is an artist and designer based in Berlin, Germany. Marie created an anonymous survey for Café Forgot&amp;rsquo;s month long residency at Larrie. Based on the chakra system, the survey is made to measure the balance of each of the seven main energy centers in the body. The final results of the survey will be treated as an indication of the overall health of the Café Forgot community. The results will act as a foundation for a collection by Marie, who is working with a methodology of integrating holistic and spiritual care to fashion objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/stand_up_comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/stand_up_comedy/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Christian DeFonte. Models: Laine Bolte, Paris Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/tuza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/tuza/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Christian DeFonte. Models: Venice W, Ada O’Higgins, Sadaf H. Naha, Blanche Apsara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>picture_room</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/picture_room/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/picture_room/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Lila Gold, Maya Laner, Rosy Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>165_duane_st</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/165_duane_st/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 20:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/165_duane_st/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Sara Grace Powell, Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Sara Grace Powell, Kat da Silva, Sabrina Fuentes, Daniela Lalita, Lulu Bonfils, Maggie Lee, Maia Ruth Lee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/temporary-wine-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/temporary-wine-bar/</guid>
      <description>Hosted by Jzuj – the collaborative cooking project of graphic designer Owen Dodd and chef Nicholas Sewitz, the wine bar spanned two evenings, providing a selection of snacks paired with natural wines. On the second night of the wine bar, opera soprano, Charlotte Jackson, provided live accompaniment, performing selected arias from the 17th-20th centuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/comedy-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/comedy-show/</guid>
      <description>Organized and curated in collaboration with friend and comedian Ruby McCollister, The Night You&amp;rsquo;ve Been Waiting For, featured performances by five comedic acts: Leah Hennessey and Emily Allan, Larry Owens, Peter Smith, Amy Zimmer, and Ruby McCollister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>170a_sufflolk_st_pt2</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_suffolk_st_pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 20:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_suffolk_st_pt2/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Katerina Tannenbaum, Erika Spring, Zoe Elise Bullock, Paulena Lynch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mirth_studio</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/mirth_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/mirth_studio/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Allegra Sussman, Christian DeFonte. Models: Hayett McCarthy, Briar McQuilkin, Bobbi Menuez, Lida Fox, Adinah Dancyger, Paris Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>170a_sufflolk_st_pt1</title>
      <link>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_sufflolk_st_pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 20:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cafeforgot.com/archive/170a_sufflolk_st_pt1/</guid>
      <description>Photography: Christian DeFonte. Model: Marland Backus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
